(Penny:)You know, I had no idea
(Penny:)Caltech is exactly
like my high school.
(Amy:)Well, it's not
exactly like it.
(Amy:)We're all
extremely smart.
(Penny:)Wow... you popular
girls are mean.
(Leonard:)I'm gonna get some coffee.
You want some?
(Sheldon:)Uh, you're really going to
have caffeine in front of me
(Sheldon:)when I'm trying to get
my life back on track?
(Leonard:)Uh, okay, let's pretend
you do have a problem.
(Howard:)I do.
You don't.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but I do.
No, you don't!
(Leonard:)But let's say you do.
(Leonard:)And don't say you do,
because you don't!
(Leonard:)Now, wouldn't you think
that throwing yourself
(Leonard:)into your work would be
the best way to deal with it?
(Sheldon:)With what?
Your problem.
(Sheldon:)I thought I didn't have
a problem.
(Howard:)That was painful
to watch.
(Raj:)So where are we going?
(Howard:)I don't know.
(Penny:)Okay.